Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/deepika-r-481b4b221 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Dialux Revit

AutoCAD

Deepika R

Electrical Design Engineer

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

I myself Deepika B.E Electrical & Electronics Engineering Graduate, having 4.5 years exp as an Electrical Design Engineer, Currently working F5 WEB SOLUTIONS – PUNE.

I work as an Electrical Designer for Building services – MEP – for projects like Retails, Commercial Buildings, Hotels, Office Building, high rise buildings.

Experience

F5 Hiring/Web Solutions
MEP Design Engineer
April 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months)
Pune, Maharashtra, India

LRT Builders

Electrical Design Engineer December 2017 - March 2022 (4 years 4 months)

Education

Karpagam Academy of Higher Education

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (April 2010 - April 2013)